Oh, one other point,
哦，还有一点
something that you'll probably run into multiple times. As we're doing this.
在这个过程中有一件事你可能会遇到很多次
If you get an error that looks like this
如果你遇到了一个类似这样的报错
eath. JS query while formatting outputs from RPC,
“[ethjs-query] 在格式化来自 RPC 的输出时”
("[ethjs-query] while formatting outputs from RPC")
nonce to high expected not to be too but got form,
“nonce 的数值过高，预期为 2 但收到的是 4”
("nonce too high Expected nonce to be 2 but got 4")
you will definitely see this a whole lot.
你肯定能看到它很多次
Here's what you do to fix this.
接下来是解决它的办法
The reason this happens is because you've closed your hardhat node and then restarted it,
发生这种情况的原因是，你曾关闭并重启了 Hardhat 的节点
and your heart had node goes, Okay, well, I'm starting fresh, I'm starting from zero.
你的 Hardhat 节点知道自己要刷新，要从零开始
But Metamask isn't smart enough to know that,
但 MetaMask 却不够智能，不知道要这样做
what we want to do is we want to come to our Metamask,
我们要做的是，前往我们的 MetaMask
we'll hit this big button, we'll go down to settings, we'll go to Advanced,
点击这个大按钮，进入“设置”("Settings")，进入“高级”("Advanced")
and we'll go to reset account.
然后点击“重置账户”("Reset Account")
And yes, we're going to reset it.
是的，我们要重置它
This isn't something ideally that you'd like to do with an actual account with actual money
理想情况下我们并不喜欢对有实际资金的真实账户做这样的操作
on a local network, this is fine.
但在本地网络上，这样做是可以的
Now if you reset the account, and you reset the node, we can go ahead and hit Confirm.
现在，如果你重置了账户也重置了节点，就可以点击“确认”("Confirm")
And it doesn't give us that error anymore.
然后它就不会给我们报那个错误了
So that's kind of the tip there,
这就是这个小提示的全部内容
you want to reset the nuts so that our Metamask and our blockchain are in sync with that nonce number.
你需要重置 nonce 以使 MetaMask 和区块链的 nonce 值达到同步